Ah, lo siento.
I'm sorry.
Finally, I was starting to think
he wouldn't show up.
I told you he would come.
Stand here.
Michael.
Hey.
What the hell is going on?
Where did you bring me?
You'll see soon enough.
Your only job is
to stand here,
smile, and stay quiet.
Give me your hand.
Dr. Ramirez, you can start now.
Thank you.
Today is a big day
for our hospital.
Henderson & Sons
is kindly investing
twenty-five million
in research
on incurable forms of lymphoma
My gratitude is endless.
Words almost fail me.
I'd like to hand over the floor
to the founder and chairman
of our benefactors.
Please welcome
Mr. Richard Henderson.
Dad.
Dad?
Thank you.
I assure you,
this is a long term commitment.
We're in this together
for decades to come.
That's why it's so important to me
that my family is here today.
My wife Sharon
my oldest son with his wife
and children,
and my youngest with his fiancée
Fiancée?